https://www.foodbankrgv.com/aboutus/privacy-policy/

Donate Now
Fighting Hunger, Feeding Hope!
Collection of Information
The Food Bank of the RGV collects certain personal information about donors, volunteers, and event participants.  We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others.  The Food Bank of the RGV is the sole owner of any information collected.  the types of information collected can include names, addresses, e-mail addresses, telephone numbers and credit card information.
Intended Use of Information
The personal information collected by the Food Bank of the RGV is used to fulfill donations, to arrange volunteering opportunities, and to send constituents details about the Food Bank RGV and its upcoming events, programs and projects.  None of the personal information collected will be disclosed to third parties unless in response to a legal claim or law enforcement agency’s request.
Opting-Out Use of Personal Information
If you do not wish to grant the Food Bank of the RGV the right to use your personal information as described, please send an email to omarir@foodbankrgv.com or call 956-682-8101.  Upon receipt of your request to opt out, the Food Bank of the RGV will remove your information from any future communications and all other uses set forth in the above sections.
Email and Postal Mail
People who donate to the Food Bank of the RGV and web site users who register with our web site are automatically subscribed to our email and US Postal mail newsletters and other Food Bank RGV publications.  You can unsubscribe from any of these by sending an email to omarir@foodbankrgv.com or calling 956-682-8101.
Links
Our website contains links to other sites.  The Food Bank of the RGV is not responsible for the privacy practices of the other sites.  When we link to a new site we will launch a new browser window.  Our privacy policy applies solely to information collected by our website.
Contacting the Food Bank of the RGV
You may contact the Food Bank of the RGV with questions or comments about this privacy policy, to update personal information, to opt out of the use of personal information, or any other matter related to the Food Bank of the RGV by emailing omarir@foodbankrgv.com or by calling 956-682-8101.
A Member of the Feeding America – The Nation’s Food Bank Network.
